Guide to the Lewis Madison Terman Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Personal and Professional Correspondence, SERIES 8
  - Johnson, Richard and David (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Johnson, Winifred (including Cree, Archer) (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - "K" Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Kelley, Truman (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Kelly, Lowell, 1930-1956 (Box 14, Folder 29-30)
  - Kinsey Data, Correspondence and material re (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Kluver, Dr. Heinrich (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - "L" Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Lai, G. B (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Lehman, Harvey C. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Library, L. M. T. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - "M" Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - McCormick, Ada P. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - MacCurdy, Robert (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - McGeoch, J. A. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Miles, Catherine C. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Miles, Walter (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - "N" Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - National Association for Gifted Children (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - National Research Council (N.R.C.) (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - National Society for the Study of Education, yearbook, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - "O" Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Oliver, R. A. C. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - "P - Q" Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Pastore, N. (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Pollack, Jack H. (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Psychological Corporation (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Psychology and Living (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Quiz Kids (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - "R" Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Raphael, Aaron W. (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Remmers, H. H., Purdue Opinion Poll (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Roback, Dr. A. A. (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Rose, Dr. Anne (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Russell, Jack (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - "S" Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Schmidt, Bernardine G. (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Scientific American (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Sex and Personality (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Shea, William T. re: TB article (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Shock, Nathan (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Simpson, B. R. (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Social Science Research Council (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Stone, C. P. (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - "T" Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Taylor, Frank J. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Terman, L. M., personal (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Thomson, Godfrey (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Thorndike, E. L. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Thorndike, Robert L. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Thurstone, L. L. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Tolman, Ruth (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - "U -W" Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 9-10)
  - Wechsler, David (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Wiggam, A. E. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Witty, Paul (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - "X-Y-Z" Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Yerkes, Robert M., 1921-1956 (Box 17, Folder 2-4)
  - Zyve Test (Stanford Scientific Aptitude Test), Correspondence re (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Grants, Projects, Conferences, Committees, SERIES 9
  - President's Office, Business Office, Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Wilbur, Dr. R. L. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Advisory Board (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Research Committee (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Aptitude Test Committee (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Semi-Centennial Anniversary Celebration (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Pick-of-the-Crop Committee (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Citizenship (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence re: Faculty & Administration at Stanford (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Committee on Selection of a President (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - National Research Council
    - General (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Research Programs (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Study of Marital Happiness: Applications, grants, and reports (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Committee Correspondence, Study of Marital Happiness (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - White House Conference on Child Health and Protection, 1929-1932 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Columbia Foundation (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Kellogg Foundation (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Marsden Foundation (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - National Institute of Health (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Office of Naval Research: Applications, reports, and correspondence (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Rosenberg Foundation (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Application for Grant to American Philosophical Society (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Sex Differences Study: Committee Correspondence and Progress Reports (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Sex Differences Research: Estimates of needs and financial reports (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Sex Research Application, etc. (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Study of Marital Happiness: miscellaneous correspondence (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Rosenberg, Max (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Heredity of Gifted Children, Search for Funds, 1923-1924 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Heredity of Gifted Children, Applications (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Gifted Funds search, 1930 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Stanford-Binet Revision: Applications for funds, grant, and progress reports (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Stanford University: Annual Reports, Gifts, and Commencement, 1919-20, 1934-35, 1935-36; 1937-38; 1938 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - University of California, Berkeley: Commencement, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 35)
- Miscellaneous Material and Correspondence, SERIES 10
  - ENGAGEMENTS, INVITATIONS, BOOK ORDERS
    - Dictionary of Psychology: outlines, correspondence (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Invitations, 1920-1942 (Box 19, Folder 2-4)
    - Engagements, 1929-1942 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Engagements and invitations, 1942-1956 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Book Orders, 1921-1946 (Box 19, Folder 7-8)
    - Classical League (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Child Welfare Research (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - National Education Association (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Cranks, 1923-1960 (Box 19, Folder 12-13)
    - Citation: "W. V. D. Bingham Lecture,", 23 March 1954 (Box 19A, Folder 1)
    - Certificate: American Psychological Association, 3 Sept. 1955 (Box 19A, Folder 2)
  - SOCIETIES AND PUBLISHERS
    - American Association of Clinical Psychologists (later the Section of Clinical Psychology of the American Psychological Association), 1917-1920 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - American Psychological Association, Addresses and letters, 1920-1955 (Box 20, Folder 2-5)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science (Pacific Division) (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - American Association for Applied Psychologists (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - American Academy for Political and Social Science (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - American Association for University Professors (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Appleton & Co. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Houghton-Mifflin, 1919-1959 (Box 20, Folder 11-14)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Co., 1935-1959 (Box 20, Folder 15-16)
    - Reader's Digest (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - World Book Co., 1920-1955 (Box 20, Folder 18-21)
  - "Committee of Ten" documents (Box 27)
  - Honors/Academic Regalia (Box 28)
- Mental and Physical Traits of Gifted Children (Genetic Studies of Genius, Vol. 1), Manuscript, SERIES 11
  - Preface, Table of Contents: First Draft (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Preface, Table of Contents: Second Draft (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - History, Nature, and Aim of Present Research: First Draft (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - History, Nature, and Aim of Present Research: Second Draft (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Method of Search for New Subjects: First Draft (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Method of Search for New Subjects: Second Draft (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Composition of the Gifted Groups: First Draft (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Composition of the Gifted Groups: Second Draft (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Racial Origin and Social Status: First Draft (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Racial Origin and Social Status: Second Draft (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Intellectually Superior Relatives: First Draft (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Intellectually Superior Relatives: Second Draft (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Vitality Statistics: First Draft (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Vitality Statistics: Second Draft (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Health and Physical History (Med. Hist.): First Draft (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Health and Physical History (Med. Hist.): Second Draft (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Medical Examinations: First Draft (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Medical Examinations: Second Draft (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - School Progress and Educational History: First Draft (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - School Progress and Educational History: Second Draft (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Tests of School Accomplishment and General Information (Ach. Tests): First Draft (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Tests of School Accomplishment and General Information (Ach. Tests): Second Draft (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Tests of Intellectual, Social, and Activity Interests: First Draft (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Tests of Intellectual, Social, and Activity Interests: Second Draft (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Trait Ratings: First Draft (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Trait Ratings: Second Draft (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Tests of Character and Personality Traits: First Draft (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Tests of Character and Personality Traits: Second Draft (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Play Life: First Draft (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Play Life: Second Draft (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Scholastic, Occupational, and Other Interests: First Draft (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Scholastic, Occupational, and Other Interests: Second Draft (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Interests; Amount and Kind of Reading (Reading of Gifted): Original Data (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Interests; Amount and Kind of Reading: First Draft (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Interests; Amount and Kind of Reading: Second Draft (Box 22, Folder 13)
- A Guide To Children's Reading, Manuscript, SERIES 12
  - Part I: Manuscript, First Draft (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Part I: Manuscript, Second Draft, and Part II: Fragments (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Parts I and II: Fragments and Further Revisions (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Margaret Bailey's Suggestions for Improvement (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Biographical Data for Genetic Studies of Genius, Vol. II, Eearly Mental Traits of 300 Geniuses, SERIES 13
  - Adams, J. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Adams, J. Q. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Addison (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Agassiz (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Alberoni (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Alfieri (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Ali Wali Zade (Ali Pasha) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Anderson (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Andrews (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Arago (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Ariosto (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Arnauld (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Atterbury (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Bach (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Bacon (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Bailly (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Balzac (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Baxter (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Bayle (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Beethoven (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Bentham (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Bentley (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Beranger (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Berkeley (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Bernadote (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Berzelius (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Beza (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Bichat (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Blake (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Blucher (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Boerhaave (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Bolivar (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Bossuet (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Boyle (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Bright (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Bronte (Charlotte) (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Brougham (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Buffon (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Bulwer (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Bunyan (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Burke (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Burnet (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Burns (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Byron (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Calderon (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Calvin (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Campanella (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Candolle (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Canning (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Canova (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Cardan (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Carlyle (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Canot (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Cervantes (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Chalmers (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Channing (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Chateaubriand (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Chatterton (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Chesterfield (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Clarendon (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Clarke (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Clive (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Cobbett (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Cobden (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - Coleridge (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Comte (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Constant (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Cook (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Copernicus (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Corneille (Box 23, Folder 70)
  - Cortez (Box 23, Folder 71)
  - Cousin (Box 23, Folder 72)
  - Cowper (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - Cranmer (Box 23, Folder 74)
  - Cromwell (Box 23, Folder 75)
  - Cuvier (Box 23, Folder 76)
  - D'Alembert (Box 23, Folder 77)
  - Danton (Box 23, Folder 78)
  - Darwin (Box 23, Folder 79)
  - Davy (Box 23, Folder 80)
  - Defoe (Box 23, Folder 81)
  - Descares (Box 23, Folder 82)
  - Dickens (Box 23, Folder 83)
  - Diderot (Box 23, Folder 84)
  - Disraeli (Box 23, Folder 85)
  - Drake (Box 23, Folder 86)
  - Dryden (Box 23, Folder 87)
  - Dumas (Box 23, Folder 88)
  - Dupin (Box 23, Folder 89)
  - Durer (Box 23, Folder 90)
  - Eliot (Box 23, Folder 91)
  - Emerson (Box 23, Folder 92)
  - Erasmus (Box 23, Folder 93)
  - Etienne (Box 23, Folder 94)
  - Faraday (Box 23, Folder 95)
  - Farragut (Box 23, Folder 96)
  - Fenelon (Box 23, Folder 97)
  - Fichte (Box 23, Folder 98)
  - Fielding (Box 23, Folder 99)
  - Fouche (Box 23, Folder 100)
  - Fox, Chas. James (Box 23, Folder 101)
  - Fox, George (Box 23, Folder 102)
  - Franklin, B. (Box 23, Folder 103)
  - Franklin, J. (Box 23, Folder 104)
  - Fulton (Box 23, Folder 105)
  - Galileo (Box 23, Folder 106)
  - Gambetta (Box 23, Folder 107)
  - Garibaldi (Box 23, Folder 108)
  - Garrison (Box 23, Folder 109)
  - Gaskell (Box 23, Folder 110)
  - Gassendi (Box 23, Folder 111)
  - Gay-Lussac (Box 23, Folder 112)
  - Gibbon (Box 23, Folder 113)
  - Gluck (Box 23, Folder 114)
  - Goethe (Box 23, Folder 115)
  - Goldsmith (Box 23, Folder 116)
  - Grant (Box 23, Folder 117)
  - Grimm (Box 23, Folder 118)
  - Grote (Box 23, Folder 119)
  - Grotius (Box 23, Folder 120)
  - Guicciardini (Box 23, Folder 121)
  - Guizot (Box 23, Folder 122)
  - Haller (Box 23, Folder 123)
  - Hamilton, A. (Box 23, Folder 124)
  - Hamilton, W. (Box 23, Folder 125)
  - Handel (Box 23, Folder 126)
  - Harvey (Box 23, Folder 127)
  - Hastings (Box 23, Folder 128)
  - Hawthorne (Box 23, Folder 129)
  - Hayden (Box 23, Folder 130)
  - Hegel (Box 23, Folder 131)
  - Heine (Box 23, Folder 132)
  - Helvetius (Box 23, Folder 133)
  - Herder (Box 23, Folder 134)
  - Herschel (Box 23, Folder 135)
  - Hobbes (Box 23, Folder 136)
  - Hogarth (Box 23, Folder 137)
  - Holberg (Box 23, Folder 138)
  - Hugo (Box 23, Folder 139)
  - Humboldt, Alexander (Box 23, Folder 140)
  - Humboldt, W. (Box 23, Folder 141)
  - Hume (Box 23, Folder 142)
  - Hunter (Box 23, Folder 143)
  - Hutgens (Box 23, Folder 144)
  - Irving (Box 23, Folder 145)
  - Jackson (Box 23, Folder 146)
  - Jansen (Box 23, Folder 147)
  - Jefferson (Box 23, Folder 148)
  - Jenner (Box 23, Folder 149)
  - Johnson (Box 23, Folder 150)
  - Jonson, B. (Box 23, Folder 151)
  - Kant (Box 23, Folder 152)
  - Kepler (Box 23, Folder 153)
  - Klopstock (Box 23, Folder 154)
  - Kotzebue (Box 23, Folder 155)
  - La Fontaine (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Lagrange (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Lamartine (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Lamennais (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - La Place (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Lavoisier (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Law (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Lee (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Leibnitz (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Leopardi (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Lessing (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - L'Hopital (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Liebig (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Lincoln (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Linnaeus (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Livingstone (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Locke (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Longfellow (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Luther (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Macaulay (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Madison (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Maintenon (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Malebranche (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Marat (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Marlborough (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Marmont (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Martineau (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Massena (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Mazarin (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Mazzini (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Mehemi Ali (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Melanchthon (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Mendelssohn (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Metastasio (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Michelangelo (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Mill, J. S. (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Miller (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Milton (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Mirabeau (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Moliere (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Monk (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Montaigne (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Montesquieu (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Moore (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - More (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Moreau (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Mozart (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Murat (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Murillo (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Musset (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Napier (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Napoleon (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Necker (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Nelson (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Newman (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Newton (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Ney (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - Niebuhr (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - O'Connell (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Oersted (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - Palestrina (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - Pascal (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Peel (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Pitt (Senior) (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - Pitt (The Younger) (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - Pope (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - Poussin (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - Prescott (Box 24, Folder 68)
  - Priestley (Box 24, Folder 69)
  - Racine (Box 24, Folder 70)
  - Raleigh (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - Raphael (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - Rembrandt (Box 24, Folder 73)
  - Renan (Box 24, Folder 74)
  - Reuchlin (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - Reynolds (Box 24, Folder 76)
  - Richelieu (Box 24, Folder 77)
  - Robertson (Box 24, Folder 78)
  - Rosebpierre (Box 24, Folder 79)
  - Rossini (Box 24, Folder 80)
  - Rubens (Box 24, Folder 81)
  - St. Cyr (Box 24, Folder 82)
  - Saint-Simon (Box 24, Folder 83)
  - Sainte-Beuve (Box 24, Folder 84)
  - Sand (Box 24, Folder 85)
  - Sarpi (Box 24, Folder 86)
  - Savonarola (Box 24, Folder 87)
  - Scaliger (Box 24, Folder 88)
  - Schelling (Box 24, Folder 89)
  - Schiller (Box 24, Folder 90)
  - Schleiermacher (Box 24, Folder 91)
  - Scott (Box 24, Folder 92)
  - Sevigne (Box 24, Folder 93)
  - Seward (Box 24, Folder 94)
  - Shaftesbury (Box 24, Folder 95)
  - Sheridan (Box 24, Folder 96)
  - Sheridan, R. B. B. (Box 24, Folder 97)
  - Sherman (Box 24, Folder 98)
  - Smith, A. (Box 24, Folder 99)
  - Southey (Box 24, Folder 100)
  - Spenser (Box 24, Folder 101)
  - Spinoza (Box 24, Folder 102)
  - Stael (Box 24, Folder 103)
  - Soult (Box 24, Folder 104)
  - Strauss (Box 24, Folder 105)
  - Sumner (Box 24, Folder 106)
  - Swedenborg (Box 24, Folder 107)
  - Swift (Box 24, Folder 108)
  - Tasso (Box 24, Folder 109)
  - Tennyson (Box 24, Folder 110)
  - Thackeray (Box 24, Folder 111)
  - Thiers (Box 24, Folder 112)
  - Thou (Box 24, Folder 113)
  - Tieck (Box 24, Folder 114)
  - Turgot (Box 24, Folder 115)
  - Van Dyck (Box 24, Folder 116)
  - de Vauban (Box 24, Folder 117)
  - de Vega (Box 24, Folder 118)
  - Velasquez (Box 24, Folder 119)
  - Vergniaud (Box 24, Folder 120)
  - Da Vinci (Box 24, Folder 121)
  - Voltaire (Box 24, Folder 122)
  - Wagner (Box 24, Folder 123)
  - Wallenstein (Box 24, Folder 124)
  - Walpole (Box 24, Folder 125)
  - Warburton (Box 24, Folder 126)
  - Washington (Box 24, Folder 127)
  - Watt (Box 24, Folder 128)
  - Weber (Box 24, Folder 129)
  - Weber (Box 24, Folder 130)
  - Webster (Box 24, Folder 131)
  - Wesley (Box 24, Folder 132)
  - Wieland (Box 24, Folder 133)
  - Wilberforce (Box 24, Folder 134)
  - Winckelmann (Box 24, Folder 135)
  - Wilkes (Box 24, Folder 136)
  - Wolsey (Box 24, Folder 137)
  - Wolf (Box 24, Folder 138)
  - Wordsworth (Box 24, Folder 139)
  - Wingli (Box 24, Folder 140)
- Study Participant Files, SERIES 14
- Additional Material, 1941-1953; Accession ARCH-1981-072
  - Terman's letters to Sadie Aaron, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Oct. 1941 letter includes memo "Results of Stanford Faculty Poll on U.S. Foreign Policy."
  - Terman's letters to Sadie Aaron, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Terman's letters to Sadie Aaron, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Terman's letters to Sadie Aaron, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Terman's letters to Sadie Aaron Caplovitz, 1948, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Grayson Kefauver to Sadie Aaron, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2014-004; 241.5 Linear feet
  - Administrative Files
    - Microfiche (Box 1)
    - Index Cards (Box 2)
    - Codebooks, Home Information Blank Forms, Binders, 1920s-1940s (Box 3)
    - Data (Box 4)
    - Microfiche (Box 5)
    - Codebooks, Binders, 1940-1986 (Box 6)
    - Codebooks (Box 7)
    - Codebooks, Marriage Study, Siblings, Sears Research (Box 8)
    - ITS Data Sheets, Codes (Box 9)
    - Offspring, Index Cards (K-Z) (Box 10)
    - Codebooks (Box 11)
    - Published Data (Box 12)
    - IBM Punch Cards, Sears Psych (Box 13)
    - Data - ITS Tab Sheets (Box 14)
    - Codebooks, 1940s-1980s (Box 15)
    - Offspring, Index Cards (A-J) (Box 16)
    - Protocols and Codebooks, 1891-1990s (Box 17)
    - Codebooks, 1920s-1930s (Box 18)
    - Old Decks, Sears Punch Cards (Box 19)
    - Microfiche (Box 20)
    - IBM Punch Cards (Girls 1,2,3,4,8,9,12,15,18) (Box 21)
    - Card Data (Box 22)
    - Codes, Life Cycle Study (Bound), 1950s (Box 23)
    - Data - Mortality (Box 24)
    - Data - Terman Study (Box 25)
    - Card Sorter and Data (Box 26)
    - Attrition Sears, Hamilton, Terman Study, 1984 (Box 27)
    - Correction on Data Files, 1960-1982 (Box 28)
    - Data (Box 29)
    - Data (Box 30)
    - Hilgard Files, A-Z, 1984-1985 (Box 31)
    - Study Data (Box 32)
    - Tab Sheets, 1922-1992 (Box 33)
    - Photographs, Terman Memorial Brochures (Box 34)
    - Old Literature, Sears, Women's Questionnaires (Box 35)
    - Follow-Up Data, Index Cards, Shneidman Interview Tapes, Married Names (Box 36)
    - Microfiche (Box 37)
    - Follow-Up Data (Box 38)
    - Follow-Up Data (Box 39)
    - Computer Printouts: General, Men's, Women's; Codebook Sears., 1956; 1972; 1937-1940 (Box 40)
  - Study Participant Files
  - Published Works
    - Books and Reprints (Box 154-160)
  - Plaster Busts - Terman (1) and child (1) (Box 161)